Guide to the UE News Photograph Collection, 1933-1998 UE.14.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Individuals and Topics, 14.1.4.
  - Strikes Mackay, Emeryville, CA (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Strikes Meetings, 1940s-1950s (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Strikes Negatives (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Strikes Posters (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Strikes Tung-sol Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Strikes Unidentified (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Strikes Violence in Philadelphia (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Steward Conference, Indianapolis, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Steward Conference, Fort Wayne (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Empty (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Sunbeam, Chicago, 1940s (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Sylvania (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Sylvania Conference, 1950-1970 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Sylvania Locals Conference, Pittsburgh, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Sylvania Organizing (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - TV-Market Square Event, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Taft-Hartley Demonstrations (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Taunton Blitz, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Them and Us, 1940s-1980s (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Together we win: UE Fox Plant, Shuster, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Tool and Die Conference, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Truman, Harry S. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - UE Class/Education, 1940s (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - UE Contract Signing Philco (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - UE Dayton Conference, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - UE Decca Conference Board, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - UE Delegation in U.S.S.R., 1980s (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - UE Delegation at Washington, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - UE Films (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - UE Joint Conference Board Meetings, 1940s (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - UE Joint Conference Board Meetings, 1950s (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - UE Joint Conference Board Meetings, 1960s (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - UE Joint Conference Board Meetings, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - UE Joint Conference Board Meetings General (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - UE Legislative Conference, Washington D.C., May, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - UE Legislative Conference, Washington D.C., June, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - UE Legislative Conference, Washington D.C., March, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - UE Legislative Conference, Washington D.C., March, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - UE National Office (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - UE National Office, 1940s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - UE News Goes to Press (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - UE Public Sector Conference, July 21, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - UE Sylvania, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - UE/FE, 1950s (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - UE/FE Executive Board (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - UE/GE General Executive Board, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - UE/GE Negotiations, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - UE/GE Negotiations, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Unemployed Councils: General (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Unemployment, General, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Unemployment Scenes (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Unemployment, Vermont, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Union in Action: Stewards, Bargaining, etc. (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - United Auto Workers (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - United Farm Workers of America (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - United Mine Workers (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - United Rubber Workers (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - United Steel Workers (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Vermont Coalition for Peace, Jobs and Justice, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Vermont Labor and Farm Council Conference, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Vermont Labor Forum Winooski Town Meeting, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Veterans Committee, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Veterans Conference, District 4, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Veterans Conference, District 6, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Veterans Conference, District 2 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Veterans Delegation, 1949 (Box 35, Folder 53)
  - Veterans, District 8 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Veterans Welfare Committee (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Volunteer Organizers (Box 35, Folder 56)
  - Voting: General (Box 35, Folder 57)
  - Wage Hearing, Hotel New Yorker, 1944 (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Wage Hearing, Washington D.C., District 8, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Wage Conference, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Wage Conference: Buffalo, New York, 1952 (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Wage Freeze Demonstrations (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Wallace Campaign, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - War Action (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - War Bonds (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - War Draftees, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - War Protest, 1960s-1970s (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - War Veterans (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - War Labor Board, GE/W Hearings (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Washington Oil Price Demonstration, District 1 and 6, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Washington D.C. Rally, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Washington Gas Conference (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Reform (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Western Electric General, 1940s (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Western Electric NLRB Hearings (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Western Electric National Conference, New York (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Western Electric Organizing Committee, 1940s (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Western Electric Veterans Committee, 1940s (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Westinghouse Conference Board, 1940s (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Westinghouse Conference Board, 1950s (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Westinghouse Conference Board, 1960s (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Westinghouse Conference Board, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Westinghouse Conference Board General (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Westinghouse Elevator Workers (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Westinghouse General, 1940s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Westinghouse General (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Westinghouse Negotiations, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Westinghouse Negotiations, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Westinghouse Negotiations, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Westinghouse Pensioners, 1940s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Westinghouse Salaried Conference, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Wire Conference, January 1985 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Women Auxiliary, 1940s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Women Conference, 1940s-1950s (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Women Conference District 7, 1949 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Women Conference, 1950, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Women Conference District 3, Schenectady, NY, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Women Conference District 11, Chicago, January 1952 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Women Conference District 9, Fort Wayne, July 1952 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Women Conference District 4 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Women Conference, 1953-1954 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Women Conference, National Conference on Problems of Working Women, May 1953 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Women Conference Washington D.C., May 1955 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Women Conference, New York City, May 1956 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Women Conference, New York City, January 1962 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Women in Leadership: Past, Present, and Future (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Women at War: Production, etc. (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Women General (Box 36, Folder 40-41)
  - Women, 1970s-1980s (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Workers in Plant (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - World Trade Union Conference, January 1945 (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - World War II (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - WFTU: World Federation of Trade Unions (Box 36, Folder 46)
- Oversize Photographs, 14.1.5.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This material was added to the finding aid in January 2011.
  - UE Convention Photographs, 1938-1944, 1946-1951, 1953-1963, 1965, 1967-1970, 1972, 1974, 1976-1980, 1982-1987, 1996, undated; 1-75. (Map-case 5, Drawer 3)
  - Photograph and Negative of Workers, 1-2. (Map-case 10, Drawer 3)
  - Production for Victory Conference, District 6, 1942; 3.
  - Children's Picketline, Local 110, 4.
  - Comparing Jackie Robinson to a Singer Sewing Machine Worker, 5.
  - Leaders of the UE: Emspak, Matles and Fitzgerald, 6.
  - Testimonial Dinner to James Matles, 1942-1943; 7-8.
  - Philip Murray Meeting on Behalf of the IUE-CIO at Turtle Creek Stadium, Local 601, 9-11.
  - 4th Annual Conference on the Problems of Working Women, 1956; 12-13.
  - UE District 6 Women's Conference, 1943; 14.
  - National Conference on the Problems of Working Women, 1962; 15.
  - United Electrical Policy Conference, 1950; 16-18.
  - Stewards' Council, Local 610, 19.
  - District 6 Conference, 20.
  - GE Strike Ratification Hearing, Local 119, 1946; 21.
  - UE Local 935, 22.
  - UE Labor Meeting, Local 251, 23.
  - Joint Gathering of the Management of Shops Under Contract, Local 155, 1942; 24.
  - 10th Anniversary Banquet in Honor of Shop Stewards, Local 155, 1944; 25.
  - UE Delegation to the GE Lamp Conference, 1945; 26-27.
  - Testimonial Banquet for Albert J. Fitzgerald, Local 201, 1941; 28.
  - Testimonial Dinner for Albert J. Fitzgerald, 1942; 29.
  - UE District 3 Delegating Conference, 30.
  - 1st Annual Stewards Banquet, Colt's Industrial Union, Local 270, 1942; 31.
  - Membership Meeting, Local 1104, 1947; 32.
  - UE $.10/Hour Victory Meeting, Local 1104, 1941; 33.
  - People's March for Jobs, Trafalgar Square, London, 1981; 34.
  - Litton Strike Photographs, 35.
  - District 4 Conference, 1944; 36.
  - UE Trenton, District 4, 37.
  - UE District 4, 38.
  - Robert B. Logsdon, International Representative, 1945; 39.
  - CIO "Win the War" Rally, 1942; 40.
  - East Pittsburgh Westinghouse Strike, Police Violence, 1916; 41.
  - Noon Gate Meeting, Local 601, April 26, 1950; 42-44.
- Chicago UE News Photographs, 14.1.6.
  The Chicago UE News was the official publication of UE Locals 1105, 1114, 1149, 1150, 1151, and 1154, which were located in Chicago. The newspaper was published twice per month from 1941 to 1948 and contained articles regarding the Chicago locals and UE District 11. This series contains the photograph archives of this short lived UE publication, documenting the Chicago locals' contribution to the World War II production effort and post-war labor struggles into the 1950s.
  - Army-Navy Production Awards, 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Local 1150 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Local 1150: Stewards' Party (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - District 11 and War Effort (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Chicago Transit Authority Picket Contact Sheets and Unidentified Meeting Photos (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Local 1119 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Local 1119: CIO Raiders Go Home (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - George Burton and Frank Gigliotti Back Pay from Elkay Manufacturing Co., 1951 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Paashe, Cory, and Unidentified Strikes (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Local 1150: Meetings (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Local 1150: Headshots and Rally (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Jergen Meeting (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Local 1150: Goodman Strike for Wage Increase (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Local 1150: GM Lab (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Local 1150: Cinch Manufacturing Corp. Back Pay (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Local 1150: American Condenser Strike and Christmas Party, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Local 1150: Advance Strike for Wage increase and Rent Control Bus Trip (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Local 1114: Employers Association of Chicago Picket (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Member Photographs (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Local 1150: Standard X-Ray Co. Pre-Election Rally Group Photo, May 11, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Pioneer Employee Meeting (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Local 1150: Parties and Softball Team (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Local 1150: Strikes and Political Demonstrations (Box 37, Folder 23)